{
  "decks": [
    {
      "id": 1,
      "name": "Rendering in React",
      "description": "React's component structure allows for quickly building a complex web application that relies on DOM manipulation. "
    },
    {
      "name": "React Router",
      "description": "React Router is a collection of navigational components that compose declaratively with your application.",
      "id": 2
    },
    {
      "name": "xcv123",
      "description": "xcv123",
      "id": 3
    },
    {
      "name": "sdfds",
      "description": "dsfsdf",
      "id": 4
    },
    {
      "name": "22222",
      "description": "2222",
      "id": 6
    },
    {
      "name": "asd",
      "description": "asd",
      "id": 9
    },
    {
      "name": "wqe",
      "description": "qwe",
      "id": 10
    }
  ],
  "cards": [
    {
      "id": 1,
      "front": "Differentiate",
      "back": "Virtual DOM updates are faster but do not directly update the HTML Differentiate",
      "deckId": 1
    },
    {
      "front": "What path will match the follow Route?\n<Route>\n  <NotFound />fssdfsd\n</Route>fvdsfvdfvdfv",
      "back": "All paths. A route with no path matches all URL'szxcvzxczxczxc",
      "deckId": 2,
      "id": 4
    },
    {
      "front": "What does <Switch> do?",
      "back": "Renders the first matching child <Route> ",
      "deckId": 2,
      "id": 5
    },
    {
      "front": "sdf",
      "back": "sdfsdf",
      "deckId": 2,
      "id": 8
    },
    {
      "front": "zxczxczxc123123123",
      "back": "zxczxczxczxc123123123",
      "deckId": 2,
      "id": 11
    },
    {
      "front": "sdfsdf",
      "back": "sdfsdf",
      "deckId": 2,
      "id": 12
    },
    {
      "front": "sfdsdf",
      "back": "sdfsdf",
      "deckId": 2,
      "id": 13
    },
    {
      "front": "fsdfsd",
      "back": "dsfsdf",
      "deckId": 2,
      "id": 14
    },
    {
      "front": "sdf",
      "back": "sdf",
      "deckId": 4,
      "id": 15
    },
    {
      "front": "dasdasd",
      "back": "asdasd",
      "deckId": 4,
      "id": 18
    },
    {
      "front": "adssad",
      "back": "asdasd",
      "deckId": 3,
      "id": 20
    },
    {
      "front": "asdasd",
      "back": "sadasd",
      "deckId": 3,
      "id": 21
    },
    {
      "front": "asd",
      "back": "asd",
      "deckId": 3,
      "id": 22
    },
    {
      "front": "zc",
      "back": "zxc",
      "deckId": 1,
      "id": 23
    },
    {
      "front": "zxc",
      "back": "zc",
      "deckId": 1,
      "id": 24
    },
    {
      "front": "asd",
      "back": "sad",
      "deckId": 9,
      "id": 25
    },
    {
      "front": "asd",
      "back": "asd",
      "deckId": 9,
      "id": 26
    },
    {
      "front": "asd",
      "back": "ad",
      "deckId": 9,
      "id": 27
    },
    {
      "front": "qwe",
      "back": "qwe",
      "deckId": 10,
      "id": 28
    }
  ]
}